W-We didn't vote!
(Leonard:)We didn't have to--
that was clearly a tangent.
(Leonard:)Now come on.
Back to work.
(Leonard:)If we're leaning towards
quantum coupling...
(Leonard:)Aah! Why?
(Sheldon:)You said
"quantum coupling."
(Sheldon:)That made me think
of the show Quantum Leap.
(Sheldon:)That's a tangent
and it's your fault.
(Howard:)That's ridiculous.
Sheldon, I vote that
is not a tangent.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
And now I owe you one.
Ow!
(Sheldon:)That was your fault.
Hey!
(Raj:)Ooh, that is a lot of hair.
Ow!
(Raj:)And now I'm gonna hear it
from Jenny.
(stammers)
Everyone stop.
(Leonard:)This was a stupid idea.
(Leonard:)Negative reinforcement
isn't working.
(Sheldon:)I think you mean
positive punishment.
(Sheldon:)Negative reinforcement is the
removal of a positive stimulus.
(Sheldon:)It's a common mistake.
(Leonard:)Negative reinforcement
is really wrong?
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's used incorrectly
all the time.
(Sheldon:)Even Bill Murray
makes that mistake
(Sheldon:)in the first scene
of Ghostbusters.
(Raj:)No way. Not Bill Murray.
(Bill Murray(on screen):)I'm studying the effect
of negative reinforcement